<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Ellen&#39;s blog!</title>
    <link>http://blog.ellenhp.me/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Ellen&#39;s blog!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 12:22:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ellenhp.me/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Canon R6 Bluetooth protocol</title>
      <link>http://blog.ellenhp.me/blog/canon_r6_bluetooth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 12:22:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ellenhp.me/blog/canon_r6_bluetooth/</guid>
      <description>I just got a Canon R6 recently and have been playing around with it. It&amp;rsquo;s really a cool piece of equipment. One thing I noticed is that the persistent Bluetooth connection seems to allow a phone to turn the camera on even when the power switch is turned to the off position. This is useful for extracting photos from the device. I&amp;rsquo;ve captured a dump of the bluetooth traffic from the Canon Camera Connect app to the R6 and will probably attempt to reverse engineer it over the coming days and weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Yubikeys for PGP with secure key backups</title>
      <link>http://blog.ellenhp.me/blog/yubikeys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 12:21:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ellenhp.me/blog/yubikeys/</guid>
      <description>This article was originally written in 2018.
First, I really ought to say that I&amp;rsquo;m not recommending people do this, because everyone has their own appetite for risk, and everyone faces different threats online. That said, I did want to write up my own approach to keeping PGP keys safe and secure while ensuring I can restore a backup if I ever need to.
Premise I recently got some Yubikeys for to use as U2F devices to lock down my Google, Facebook, Github and Twitter accounts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>